New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
1952-1964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Board of Mediation
5581
115 cubic feet
115 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records of specific mediation cases from the New York State Board of Mediation.
5667673
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Randy Kelley, August 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 20, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Mediation and conciliation, Industrial--New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial--New York (State); New York (State). Board of Mediation.
5667673
- A 1 - A 11, A 100 - A 189 (1938). (Box 1)
  - SAML Gordon, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ranch Meat Markets, Inc. Harry Olstein, Pres., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Stationery, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Scrap Iron and Steel Institute, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Michael, Raymond S. trading as Savoy Shops, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - M & M Kiddie Shop, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Eugene Modell Radio and Tel. Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1027 Westchester Avenue Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. Goodman, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - La Valle, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Strauss Fasteners, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - All Brands Tire Exchange, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Oriental Paper Box Mfg., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pinaud Incorporated, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fybro Refrigerator Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - La Salle Watch Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Orzechowski Provision Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ramsey Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Principal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Jerome Specialty Shop, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Loramine Drug, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Royal Office and Supply, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Standard Body Corporation, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Meyer's Stationery, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Two Ninety-Nine Broadway, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Silver Rod Stores Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lane Jewelry, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - J. Rabinovich, Inc. and Solesto, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Goodseit and Sonnenschein doing business under "Levine Bros", 1938 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Schwartz Bros. Mill Enterprise, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - California Grape Products Co. Ltd., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Suffolk County Truck Owners Assn., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Long Island Mattress Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - H.H. Waters Jewelry Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Meat Dealers, Ye Old New York Branch of N.Y. State Assn. of Retail (S. Mansbach), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kartineger and Niedenberg, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Riveria Pharmacy. Jay-Arr Drug Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Wholesale Fresh Water Fish Merchants, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Knickerbocker Stationery, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - A. Werman Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Kraft Associated Distributors, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Capitol Paint & Varnish Works, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Studio Apartments, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Richard Schnibbe, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ludwig Baumann, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Tiara Products Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - New England Curtain Shop, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Morris Abrams, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Progressive Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Jacob Schoenfeld, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Merribee Art Embroidery Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Glaser Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Oxenberg Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Vermite Exterminating Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - United States Lines Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Strike of Misc. Labor, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Reliable Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Madow's, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Champion Shoe Manufacturing Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Consolidated Tinware Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Mace Company (Textile Workers Org. Committee), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - I. Gralla, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - B. Cribari & Sons, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Siegel's Drug Store, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - P.B. Baking Co., H and H Baking Co., Princeton Baking Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Hoover Sales Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Daniel Jones, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Goldman Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - William Goldblum & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Astor Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Hara, Irving, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Firor, Frank M., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Gottbetter Brothers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Rothberg and Katz, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Swan Laundry, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Roman Macaroni Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - A.T. Concord & Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Coyne & Delaney Corporation, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Stevens, Walter B. and Son, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - United States Cloth Cutting Machine Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Smoked Fish Industries (Employers), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Weil and Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Louis Seiler Furniture Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - L. Somomon & Son, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Benay Art Embroidery Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - David Karron, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Malina Company, Inc. and Bendythe Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Undergarment and Negligee Workers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Seeman Bros., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Automotive Specialty Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Bellows & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - E.J. Barry Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Lacidem Realty Corporation, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Hills Brothers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Komfort Mattress, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Glove Manufacturers Arbitration, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - David Bogen Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - 1938 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Monastersky Rubin, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Savoy Decorators, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - H. Fleisig, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - United-Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Garrett & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Ormont Machine Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - B. Kittay and Sons, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Sunshine Radio System, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- A 190 - A 368 (1938- ). (Box 2)
  - Monastersky, Rubin, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Savoy Decorators, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - H. Fleisig, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - United-Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Garrett & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ormont Machine Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - B. Kittay and Sons, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sunshine Radio System, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Square Music and Sport Shop, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Gotbetter Brothers, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Handy and Specialty Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Modern Refrigerator Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Goldman, Benjamin, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jerome Hosiery and Underwear Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Super Metal Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Wirklich, Joseph (Estate of), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Royal Office Supply Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - William Weinberg Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rockwell's Bakery, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sky Chief Radio Corporation, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Roberts Radio Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Stoller, Dora (Estate of), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Globe-Brenner Corporation, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - F.A. Schurmann, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Superior Dairy Products, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Goldberg, N., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Grandview Dairies, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Scall Undergarment Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers of America, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Aaron Streit, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Olympia Baking Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Smartwear Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Princely Products, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Radin Fish Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Venice Curtain Stores Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Steinhardt Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Kumfort Mattress Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Horowitz Bros. and Margareten, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Municipal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Eveready Hardware Mfg. Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Michael Vitolo, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - (Blum, Frank, Fishkin) Ye Olde N.Y. Branch, N.Y. State Assn. of Retail Meat Dealers, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - S. Beckenstein, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Mutual Sewing Machine Dealers, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Krasnoff Dental Laboratories, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Pioneer Watch Case Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mayer and Herman Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Kesselman's Department Store, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Manhattan Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Bristol Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dubrow Pure Food Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - New York and Brooklyn Casket Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - S. and W. Fine Foods, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Marcus Box Spring Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - New York Federation of Food Merchants, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - S. and B. Stores, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Service Headquarters Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Principal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - WM. A. Taylor and Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Transformer Corporation of America, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Mayer Harman Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Fur Machine Dealers Association, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Levinson Photo Service, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Sclafani Import Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Yelloway Transportation Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Paramount Silk House, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Samuel Klein and Sons`, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Principal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Eveready Hardware Mfg. Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Wholesale Tobacco Distributors of New York, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Rosola Food Products, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Ormont Machine Co. Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Accurate Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Lane Jewelry Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Progress Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Block Drug Stores Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Broadway Central Hotel, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Rayburn Cafeteria Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - T. Freedman, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - La Valle Shoe Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Weil Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Hara, James, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Wolf Paper Box Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Lion binding and Trimming Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hotel St. George, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Kaplan, Philip, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Janus Operating Co., Inc. (Golden Crest Holding Corp.), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Anker's Decorators, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Reliable Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Pincus Curtain Store, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Stahl Meyer Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - 1005 Jerome Avenue (Fee Equities Inc.), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Saporta, O., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- A 370 - A 507 (1938). (Box 3)
  - William Weinberger (N.Y. State Assn. of Retail Meat Dealers, Inc.), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - National Hardware Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Window Cleaning Co., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Queens borough Farm Products Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Dairy, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - J. Pressman and Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Display Well Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - National Shoe Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Stamp Works, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Union Cutlery Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Six Seventy Seven, Local and Eleven Eighty Five, Local, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Triangle Bus Corp., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bronx Retail Meat Dealers Assn., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Englander Bed Spring Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Plaza Auto Body Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Riviera Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pinaud, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dobrin Supply Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cornelia Footwear, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Schlesinger Bros., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Incorporated, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Goldman's Yarn Store, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Weylin Pharmacy, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Schwartz, Samuel S., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Putterman Footwear Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Madow's, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Jones, William C., Envelope Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, David, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Pilgrim Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Midtown Hotel operating Cadillac Hotel, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Louis Cohen and Son, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - George Schaefer and Sons, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - W.E. Pruden Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bayside and Quick Delivery Co., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Nathan Baer Candy Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Mount Vernon Die Casting Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Barry Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - John Casale, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Traders Trucking Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mauro, Michael, Member, Bronx Wash. Hts. Br. Retail Meat Dealers, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Royal Butchers, member, Bronx and Wash. Hts. Br. Retail Meat Dealers, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 208 West 148th St. Realty Corp., 259 West 143rd Street, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Dumont Electric Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bias Fabric Manufacturers. Assn., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Municipal Shoe Co. Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Sheffield Farms Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Philson Manufacturing Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Edway Meat Market, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Warner Furniture Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Cleaners and Dyers BD of Trade Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Freedman's (Tillie Freedman), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Five Star Shoe Company Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Arnold Constable and Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Peller and Silverman, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bellecraft Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Greenwood Cemetery Association, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Thompson Co., John R., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Dictograph Products Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - J.H. Semel and Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Fourteenth Street Store, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Master Dy Cleaning Chain Store Operators Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - La Valle Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Astor Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - La Salle Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - National Hardware Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - American Beverage, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cohn and Rosenberger Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Davega City Radio, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Rose, Frank and Adler, Sam, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Maxwell, Jack, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Werman's, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Bluestone Photoprint Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Benenson Realty Corporation (1018 E. 163rd Street), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Dorsen Wolf Drug Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Intner, William Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Purepac Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Truitt Shoe Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Consolidated Tinware Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Savoy Specialty Shop, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Schenley Import Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Hercules Shoe Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Hayden Drug Shop, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Belfert Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Henry Romeike Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Westchester Service Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Weiner Bros., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti Nazi League, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Sam Ader, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Eugene Modell Radio and Television Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Micamold Radio Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Coal Merchants Association Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Jacob, H. and Sons, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Garden Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Modell Radio Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Landau, Henry, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Piser and Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Monastersky, Rubin, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - F. and R. Mattress Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Boro Paper Box Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- A 507 - A 713 (1939). (Box 4)
  - Loft, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Progress Shoe Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bookstaver, B.S. Dr., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - European Radio Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Abbey Photo Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Paragon Slipper Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Riggs Restaurant, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - L. and B. Hosiery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Earlswood Court Realty Corporation - Premises 351 St. Nicholas Ave., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Intner Company, William Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Table Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Jones Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Katz, M. and Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Well Made Parlor Frame Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Koestler Bros. Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Warner Furniture Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mendel Drug Store, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - W.H. Joseph and Son, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Lanner Bros., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Graham Motors, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Art Steel Company Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Goldman's Yarns, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Original Dave's, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Association of Bedding Manufacturers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kumfort Bedding Manufacturer Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Julius Altschul Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Eighteen Fiftyone Seventh Avenue Holding (1851 Seventh Ave. Holding Corp.), 1939 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Radio Tube Trading Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Luria, M.S., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dempsey, WM. S. Realty Co. (Controlling 574 St. Nicholas Ave.), 1939 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cooper Radio and Sport Shop, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Micamold Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - May Knitting Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Le Winter Radio Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Champion Shoe Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mayer Herman Shoe Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Principle Shoe Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kumfort Bedding, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Long Island Macaroni Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Lebensfeld Brothers, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Standard Flashlight Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bond Brothers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Nancy Lee Millinery, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - John R. Thompson Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Diamond Candle Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - J.B. Slattery and Bro., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Fairchild Aerial Camera Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Embassy Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Associated Plastering Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Blacharsky, S., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Wachtel, J. Biscuit Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Levenson, Jack, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Edgar Guifrida Millinery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Bernheimer Co., G.A., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Lesell Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Jeannette's Millinery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Indelacato, Joe, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Fay's Millinery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Beyda and Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Grobifker, Nathan c/o Kanter's Department Store, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Associated Marble Manufacturers Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Weiser's Ladies Shop, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Weiss Bros., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Deitz, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Restaurant Guild Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Kaufman Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Excellent Housekeeping Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Sol Broome and Co. Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Automatic Woven Wire Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Daly Millinery Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Rubenstein's Beigel Bakery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Greater New York Glazers Assn. Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Formfitting Slipper Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Decca Records, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Stolpen Cigar Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Famous Dairy Cafeteria, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Max Nadell, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Paper Box Credit Bureau, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Abraham Gerstenzang, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - United Parcel Service, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Audak Company, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - I.B. Kleinert Rubber Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Wreckers and Excavators Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - G.N.O. Drug Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - United Cigar Whelen Stores Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Lee Mart Cigar and Candy Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Berry Bedding Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Superior Drug Service`, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Buckingham Pharmacy Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Janpolis, Max, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Fishkin, Julius, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cohen, Benjamin, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Manoil Manufacturing Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Merit Kingston Cheese Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Spanier, Aaron, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - F.H.S. Cigar Stores, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Spear and Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Madow's Jewelry Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Gotbetter Brothers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Friedman's Sport Shop Philip Sulitan, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - L. Borg, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Mercantile Drug, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Elite Specialty Metal Company`, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Royal Meat Market, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Samuel Meyers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Lazar's Department Store, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 110)